Start lapping and please welcome [applause]
Gaurav [cheering voice] Maddaan.
[cheering]
[applause]
Hello guys, hi.
I had given money to all of them.  [laughs]
No, I think if he had come in a vest, they would have
recognized him quickly.  Isn't it?  Some people may
not know.  I was on the recent episode
of Dance India Dance.  [laughs]
I did a great break dance there.
No, I went to India late and paid and
wore a vest.
Meaning there were more clothes.  [laughter] I didn't
just go in a vest.   It's been
a couple of weeks.  It's been two weeks since the
episode's release and I thought people would start
recognizing me.  I have been roaming around Koramangala since morning.
[applause]
[cheering] I could
n't even get a dog.
[Praise]
My own barber is a
big fan of Latent.  Ok.  He is
not recognizing me.  [laughter]
He's watching the episode of Latent in front of me.
[laughs]
And I'm performing in it.
[laughter] You're
telling me why don't you
do something like this?
When I took off my shirt and showed it to him
[laughs]
then he said, hey you were in Dance India Dance.
Just when I was coming, a guy
recognized me on the road.  Meaning I was coming on a bike.
He recognized me from inside the helmet and
stopped me.  I said, what happened brother,
a little bit?  I mean, what did you watch on YouTube
?  What about on Instagram?  So he put
forward the breathalyzer.  [laughter] At
first I didn't understand it was a breathalyzer.
I am saying in it that I would like to
thank my parents.  [laughter] I
met two guys outside.  He said take the photo.
I said yes, take it brother.  Then he said, now I am
in a vest.  [laughs]
What kind of image have I created, brother?
[laughs]
I've even had brand people come to me asking me to do
their ad but to get naked once.
[laughs] They're
telling me I'm seeing ads for undergarments.
I said brother, I am
not comfortable with that.  He is saying,
try wearing this bra once.
[laughs]
I always felt that you could choose any career.
One day I will have to take off my clothes.
[laughter]
That's what happened to me.   The
response from the people was very good.   The
comments were even better.  I was reading the comments like this.
As soon as the episode was premiering on YouTube, the
first comment on it was that
you need a hospital, not a gym.
[laughs] The
video hasn't reached 150 likes or 150 views yet.
[laughter]
Someone once wrote that it's not easy to
insult yourself and make others laugh.
I said I was not insulting.
[laughs]
When I was up there on stage, I was like
trying to embrace my
insecurities.  This is what people told me.
I wasn't thinking.  [laughs]
When I went in the vest, I
went in because I look worse in a T-shirt.
[laughter] There's
a guy writing that this is so much better than
Sunil Paul's comedy.   What
kind of benchmark is this brother [laughs]
that you are better but Sunil Pass it is like
saying that brother you have eaten idli from there, it is
tastier than [ __ ],
why are you eating [ __ ]?
Either people are comparing him with Sunil Pal
or Arijit Singh.  They are tagging him and writing
that he is maintaining silence.  [laughs]
My friends are asking me if I'm
getting female attention.  DM
on Instagram.  My DM is full of guys.
[laughter]
Everyone has the same question about the protein you got for Rs 5 lakh.
What did you do with it?  [laughs] Brother, I
went to SBI and got an FD done.
Mere ko hinge pe ladde super like bech ke
protein maang raha hai.  [laughter]
I walk past the gym and I walk past the ass crack.
[laughter] So that no one can recover the
protein.   I feel like an
aunty who doesn't go out wearing jewellery on a dark night
[laughs].
People think that they have given me protein worth Rs 5 lakh at once and told me to
go and consume it.
I contacted him and asked, brother, when are you sending the
protein?  He said we had not even made this much.
[laughter][applause]
[applause]
Speaking of, we'll order from the Mother Place ourselves.
[laughs]
Then send it to you, we [ __ ] are boiling eggs and
eating them ourselves, friend.  [Laughter] I was afraid he might
send me five hens in the name of protein, thinking they would keep laying eggs.
[laughter]
That's your protein.
When I was coming home after shooting the episode,
my roommate was clearing a store room to
keep the protein there.  [laughter]
Brother, they told me that they will
send you little by little in shipments.
Okay and whatever your size,
100 grams will be sent in a month.
[Applause]
[Laughter]
I have consumed a total of ₹300 worth of protein in my life till date.
Ok?  My daily
protein intake is fulfilled by eating aloo bhujia
[laughs].   At
that time, a girl made a reel
on me and was saying that this boy is
very underrated.  How does it only have 400
followers yet?  There should have been a lot
more of this.  Isn't it?  That reel went so
viral that the guy has over 400
followers [laughs].   On top of that,
a boy has commented that
I am also one of those 400 followers, I
follow him, I don't go to his profile, I
follow him [laughs] but it
means I am getting some female attention also.
I will not lie like this.  DMs are coming
and girls are asking me about
my diet [laughs]
which diet do you follow Bhaiya, I don't know
what, one girl directly
wrote in it that send nudes
[laughs]
I said I don't
want to see myself naked, friend why do you want to see, she
said send it quickly, it is a KB file,
send it [laughs]
[appreciation]
I sent it [sound of clearing throat] she is
saying now send it in a vest.
Another rumour was spreading that this guy
works in Microsoft [laughs] and earns Rs
1 crore in a month.
In the comments below, people are fighting with him saying that
looking at him, it seems he earns Rs 1 crore in a month.
Usually when someone has a journey like this,
people ask, how was your journey from here to here
?  In my case the opposite is happening.  I
asked you, sisterfucker, Microsoft, one
crore
latent pay vest [laughs]
I ask you.  Money or identity?
Money money follows my brother.  Money Follows
[Encouraging voice] There are
some people who don't know Hindi
but still they are watching Latent.  I do
n't know why [laughs]
what happened to them?
Just for Time What do
you like about time?   He
is fair.
Why am I feeling scared right now?  [laughter]
You're all from here.  Are you bored?
Working Together.
Working Together.  Why does this seem like a team outing to
me?  [laughter]
Which office is yours?
Yes.  I will put it on YouTube now.
[Encouraging voice]
By the way, I am from Haryana.  Is anyone here?
From Haryana?  Sir, are you from Haryana?  What do you
do now?
Income
[laughter]
How many people did you bring along?
This is the Joint Commissioner, sir.
ADP
ED
[laughs] Well
mine is chill.  [laughter]
You think about yourself.  I don't have Jobv.
[laughter]
And which one of you was planning on coming on the show today
?  Sir, it was your plan.  You see
India's got late.  [laughter]
I mean, well, that
means it's part of your job,
everyone.  [laughter]
[applause]
Now it's mandatory for everyone.  Isn't it
for all of you?  [laughs]
I get someone else to do the crowd work.
I'm getting a little teary.  [laughter]
And you three came and sat in the front row.
[laughter]
What did I say?  I am from Haryana and I am
from Sirsa in Haryana sir.  Ok.
Maybe that's why I feel now that I should
n't tell the details, sir.  Why did I tell you
?
[laughter]
You'll find out the rest.
That district comes under his jurisdiction
[laughter] My
career started today only
[laughter] [appreciation]
FIR follows my brother
[appreciation]